

Portfolio: matthewfarquharson.design Email: matthewfarquharson@gmail.com

UX/UI Designer

Minneapolis, MN

Phone: 763-607-7210

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/matthewfarq

Summary

With a passion for user research and information architecture. I think that by studying and observing cognitive and behavioral patterns, one can design an experience with the ability to influence human behavior. If you're interested in working with someone who values the importance of designing user centered products while improving the ROI of a company, please reach out. I'd love to talk with you.

Projects

Ballistic | May 2020

Lead UX / UI Designer

Ballistic is a mobile marketplace app designed for the modern gamer. Users can purchase games, customize their prefferences, and stay up to date with the latest industry trends.

Kudu | March 2020

Lead UX / UI Designer

Designed for both desktop and mobile devices, Kudu is a social media management platform that empowers digital content creators to manage, share, and track thier assets.

Experience

Thinkful Apprenticeship | Product Design Flex | October 2019 – June 2020

- Learned industry best practices and design process standards with a focus on UX research, visual design, and front-end development.
- Created and deployed projects while learning new tools and frameworks by collaborating several hours every week with a lead product designer at AWS.

Quinn Violins & Fret Central | Sales Representative | May 2018 - Present

- By familiarizing myself with common customer questions, I made it my goal to design user centered product listings that enabled customers to make online purchases without any assistance.
- After doing this, the music shop noticed an increase in online sales, and experienced their most profitable quarter of their 20+ years of business.

Education Skills

University of Colorado, Boulder

Bachelor of Music, Violin Performance GPA: 3.6 | 2013 – 2018

User Research
Wireframing
Prototyping
Figma
InVision

User Flows
Mockups
Usability Testing
Sketch
HTML/CSS